<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <atom:link href="https://yts.am/rss/0/1080p/action/7" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <title>YTS RSS</title>
        <description>Most popular Torrents in the smallest file size RSS Feed</description>
        <link>https://yts.am/</link>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:35:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title><![CDATA[Vanishing Point (1971) [BluRay] [1080p] [YTS.AM]]]></title>
                <description><![CDATA[<a href="https://yts.am/movie/vanishing-point-1971"><img src="https://yts.am/assets/images/movies/vanishing_point_1971/medium-cover.jpg" alt="Vanishing Point (1971)" /></a><br />IMDB Rating: 7.3/10<br />Genre: Action / Crime / Thriller<br />Size: 1.56 GB<br />Runtime: 1hr 39 min<br /><br />Kowalski works for a car delivery service. He takes delivery of a 1970 Dodge Challenger to take from Colorado to San Francisco, California. Shortly after pickup, he takes a bet to get the car there in less than 15 hours. After a few run-ins with motorcycle cops and highway patrol they start a chase to bring him into custody. Along the way, Kowalski is guided by Supersoul - a blind DJ with a police radio scanner. Throw in lots of chase scenes, gay hitchhikers, a naked woman riding a motorbike, lots of Mopar and you've got a great cult hit from the early 70's.]]></description>
                <link>https://yts.am/movie/vanishing-point-1971</link>
                <guid>https://yts.am/movie/vanishing-point-1971#1080p</guid>
                <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 08:15:43 +0200</pubDate>
                <enclosure url="https://yts.am/torrent/download/ED6954FF6FC115D922FDCD3B708C406401F01F5D" type="application/x-bittorrent" length="10000" />
            </item>
            <item>
                <title><![CDATA[Incredibles 2 (2018) [WEBRip] [1080p] [YTS.AM]]]></title>
                <description><![CDATA[<a href="https://yts.am/movie/incredibles-2-2018"><img src="https://yts.am/assets/images/movies/incredibles_2_2018/medium-cover.jpg" alt="Incredibles 2 (2018)" /></a><br />IMDB Rating: 8.0/10<br />Genre: Action / Adventure / Animation / Comedy / Family / Sci-Fi<br />Size: 1.87 GB<br />Runtime: 1hr 58 min<br /><br />While the Parr family has accepted its collective calling as superheroes, the fact remains that their special heroism is still illegal. After they are arrested after unsuccessfully trying to stop the Underminer, their future seems bleak. However, the wealthy Deavor siblings of Devtech offer new hope with a bold project to rehabilitate the public image and legal status of Supers, with Elastigirl being assigned on point to be the shining example. Now having agreed for now to stay at home to care of the kids, Mr. Incredible finds domestic life a daunting challenge, especially with baby Jack-Jack's newly emerged powers making him almost impossible to manage. However, Elastigirl soon has her own concerns dealing with the menace of a new supervillain, Screenslaver, who is wreaking havoc with his mind control abilities. Now, Elastigirl must solve the mystery of this enemy, who has malevolent designs on the world with the Parr family and friends key targets of this evil.]]></description>
                <link>https://yts.am/movie/incredibles-2-2018</link>
                <guid>https://yts.am/movie/incredibles-2-2018#1080p</guid>
                <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 03:28:02 +0200</pubDate>
                <enclosure url="https://yts.am/torrent/download/6B7469C830B624321F843A95D0BD162AAF2ABFF4" type="application/x-bittorrent" length="10000" />
            </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>